<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks | Re:produce Workshop on Open Data, Materials and Code</title>
    <link>/talk/</link>
      <atom:link href="/talk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© University of Southern Queensland `2019` under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License</copyright>
    <image>
      <url>/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</title>
      <link>/talk/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emerson&#39;s Talk Title Here</title>
      <link>/talk/presentation_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/presentation_2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emerson M. Del Ponte is Associate Professor of Plant Pathology at the Universidade Federal de Viçosa (UFV), Brazil. Dr. Del Ponte has taken a leading role in teaching (Epidemiology and data science) and mentoring undergraduate and graduate students and in building an internationally-recognized research program in Plant Disease Epidemiology. From international experiences gained early in his career to continuing visits and attendance of scientific meetings and offering workshops worldwide, Dr. Del Ponte has been able to build and expand an international collaborative network in the field. His program has made important contributions to increase understanding of plant diseases of major importance to agriculture of Brazil and worldwide as well as to develop methods for enhancing epidemiological research and applications. Del Ponte is an experience reviewer and Senior Editor, currently serving as Editor in Chief of Tropical Plant Pathology. He chairs an internationally recognized graduate program in Plant Pathology of UFV. Recently, he has co-founded Open Plant Pathology, a global community a community of multidisciplinary scientists who support all forms of Open Science practices.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Data, Materials and Code Introduction</title>
      <link>/talk/presentation_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/presentation_1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
